heat.co.za 2008-04-19

# heat - This Week's hottest celebrity news

## heat Privacy Policy

_**heat**_ is committed to user privacy on our website. _**heat**_ encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all websites you visit.  

Below is a summary of heat's online privacy policy:

### Personal Information

Your personal information is used in the following ways:

  * User IDs and Passwords. Provides you with access to your profile areas and to protected content.

  * Email Correspondence. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about heat, our products, and services.

We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected.  

We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.

### Security Measures

We protect the personal information you share with us:

**1) Data Retention**  
_**heat**_ will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**2) Linked Websites**  
We provide links to third party websites. Since we do not control these Websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party websites.

### Advertising

We may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown.  

These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you.  

Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact.

### Policy updates

All updates to this policy will be posted here.  
Last update: **1 June 2007**  

Kate Moss is the UK's best dressed woman (again!).

If Heidi Klum offered to give my wardrobe a make-over. . .
